现在  你已经看到为Weather表创建的WeatherEntry类
Now, that you've seen the WeatherEntry class for
接下来就是你的任务了
the weather table, it's your turn.
在LocationEntry内部合约类中
Add the constants for
给Location表添加一些常量
the location table in the LocationEntry inner contract class.
这些常量包括表名称以及每一列的名称
These constants included the table name, and the name of each column.
正如我们在之前的图表中展示的那样
As we've shown in a few previous diagrams, the columns need to store
这些列需要存储地点设置  纬度  经度以及城市名
the location setting, latitude, longitude, and the city name.
当你编写完地点实体类的代码后
After you finish coding the location entry class,
确保你已经看过了解决方案视频
make sure to look at the solution video.
你最好使用和我们相同的常量名  因为在编写其他类的代码的时候
You'll want to use the same constant names that we use, since the code in
依赖的这些常量名是相同的
the other classes you received relies on these constant names being the same.
一旦完成
Once you've finished,
你就会定义完所有表的所有列名
you will have defined all of the columns for both of the tables.
接着  我们就准备好使用这些列名去数据库中创建
Next, we'll be ready to use these column names to actually create the tables
我们的表
in the database.